isango.com 2014-11-21

# Terms of use : isango!

### Privacy Policy

This is the privacy policy of isango! Limited, a company incorporated in England and Wales, with registered offices at TUI Travel PLC, TUI Travel House, Crawley Business Quarter, Fleming Way, Crawley, West Sussex RH10 9QL. Isango! Limited is a member of the TUI Travel PLC group of companies.

isango! understands and respects the importance of your privacy and visitors to our websites can be assured that the protection of privacy is given the highest possible priority. All personal information that we collect is used and held to comply in every way possible with the Data Protection Act 1998. isango! only obtains personal information from you if we ask for it and you provide it to us. Please read on to understand how we use the information you give us before using the isango! web pages. Please note use of the isango! web pages and services is conditional upon you agreeing to be bound by this privacy policy.

#### The information we collect

Personal information is collected when you make a reservation request or purchase something from our website, as well as when you contact us about a purchase either by email, letter, fax or on the phone. We may also collect personal information from you from any online registrations including but not limited to subscriptions, newsletters, surveys or competitions etc.

When you visit our Web pages our Web server automatically recognizes your network domain name and we collect your domain name.

When you visit our Web pages you are free to remain anonymous. However, in order to communicate with us or order a product it is necessary for you to disclose personal information. We only collect the personal information which you disclose to us, such as when you place a booking or make a purchase online. If you do not provide your personal information we may be unable to fulfill your booking or purchase.

No other collections of personal information will occur without your consent.

#### Our Security and Storage Measures

We will endeavour to take all reasonable steps to keep secure any information which we hold about you, and to keep this information accurate and up to date. We use industry-standard encryption protocols when transferring and receiving your personal information exchanged with our Web pages. When you transfer personal information to us we require that a 'secure session' first be established using Secure Socket Layer (SSL).

Your personal information is stored in secure operating environments that are not accessible by the general public. We have put security measures in place at our physical facilities to protect against the loss, misuse or alteration of your personal information by our employees or other parties.

However, no data transmission over the Internet can be guaranteed to be 100% secure, so we cannot give an absolute assurance that the information you provide to us will be secure at all times. isango! will not be held responsible for events arising from unauthorized access to your personal information.

#### Cookies

We may, from time to time, use 'cookies' to store your preferences, record session information and collect information on how you visit and access our Web pages. We collect information on the Web pages visited by our customers in order to help us to continue improving our services.

'Cookies' are pieces of information that our Web page transfers to your computer's hard disk for record-keeping purposes. Cookies can make the Web more useful by storing information about your preferences on a particular site. The use of cookies is an industry standard and many Web sites use them to provide useful features for you. Cookies in and of themselves do not personally identify you, only your computer is identified.

**There are two types of cookies:**

**1\. Session cookies**

These are used to maintain something called session state. If you consider your journey through the website as a conversation with us, this cookie reminds the site where we are in that conversation (for instance, if at some point in the conversation you asked us to add a hotel to your basket, next time you click on the basket it will still be there). Session cookies are required for the website to function but are not used in any way to identify you personally.

**2\. Permanent cookies**

When you visit our website, we will assign a permanent cookie on the hard drive of your computer. You can view these by looking in the cookies directory of your browser installation. As the name implies, permanent cookies last for a long time and each time you visit our website you send us a copy of them allowing us to identify you from visit to visit. For instance, if you were looking at hotels in London last time you were on the website and the next time you visit us we have a great hotel deal, this cookie enables us to recognise your computer, so that we can show you that deal. The aim is to enhance your experience whilst on the website and make sure you don’t miss out on great offers. Cookies do not contain any Personal Information for example, your name, address, email address, or telephone number, but simply a unique identification number that identifies your computer to us.

#### Third party tracking devices

You will see that we carry advertising relating to third parties on our website. This advertising is served either directly by third party advertisers or on their behalf by advertising network companies. These advertisers or advertising networks may place cookies, action tags or other tracking devices on your hard drive to assess the effectiveness of their ads. They may aggregate information about your visits to our website and other websites retrieved via such cookies with other information that you may have provided directly to the relevant advertiser or ad network. This Privacy Policy does not cover the use of cookies and other tracking devices by third parties. This will be covered by that third party’s privacy policies and practice and we would recommend that you take a look at these which in most cases will be found on that company’s website.

#### Opting out

You cannot block "session" cookies as they are required for our website to function correctly, but you can configure your Internet browser so that it can reject both "permanent" and "third party" cookies. Please refer to the relevant Internet browser manufacturer's website where you should be able to receive all the information you need.

All modern browsers allow you to change your cookie settings. These settings will typically be found in the 'options' or 'preferences' menu of your browser. In order to understand these settings, the following links may be helpful, otherwise you should use the 'Help' option in your browser for more details.

If you would like to find out more about cookies and their use on the Internet, you may find the following links useful:

The IAB has provided the following website to give information specifically about privacy issues around Internet advertising: [youronlinechoices.co.uk/uk](http://www.youronlinechoices.com/uk/)

For further legal information about privacy issues, you may find these links useful:

#### How We Use Your Personal Information

We use your personal information to enable us and our service partners to provide you with the information you request about our products, to fulfill your bookings, to confirm your purchases and to ensure you are correctly billed. The personal information we collect from you will be shared with our service partners who are involved in fulfilling the purchases you have made from us. Please note information may therefore be supplied outside of the UK and the European Economic Area, and the USA. Please also note that our products may be made available through our distribution partners. This privacy statement should be read in conjunction with the privacy statements of our distribution partners, which may differ from isango!'s privacy policy. isango! are not responsible for the content of or privacy policies of other web sites to which this site may link or be linked from.

We or our service partners may from time to time send you information about our new products or ask your opinion on new product initiatives so that we may improve our service to you and other consumers. If you do not want isango! to contact you in the future please ensure you check the tick boxes where we indicate at various points within the site.

Third-Party Web Beacons: We use third-party web beacons from Yahoo! to help analyze where visitors go and what they do while visiting our website. Yahoo! may also use anonymous information about your visits to this and other websites in order to improve its products and services and provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by Yahoo!, [click here.](https://reports.web.analytics.yahoo.com/optout,OptOut.vm)

We do not share your personal information with third party organizations who are not involved in fulfilling the purchases you have made from us or as described above.

#### Contacting Us

If you have any questions regarding our Privacy Policy or you would like a summary of the personal information we hold, send an e-mail to support@Isango.com. Information will only be sent to the email address on file for the customer name associated with it. We will endeavor to respond to your questions or concerns within 7 days.
